{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5348","name":"Hard Bodies Bar","address":"7443 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821","owner":"Marija Dedvukaj","licenseNumber":"208187","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.13537,42.33087","geojson":{"id":"5348","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.135367184,42.330872958]},"properties":{"name":"Hard Bodies Bar","owner":"Marija Dedvukaj","address":"7443 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"208187","establishmentid":"5348","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"10/13/2016"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"743","name":"Freer Bar","address":"7355 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"758","name":"Alaskan Bar Homestead #3","address":"7625 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"2285","name":"Little Caesar's Pizza","address":"7633 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3914","name":"Subway #29822","address":"7300 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"1009","name":"General George Patton Post #11","address":"4930 Central","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"2073","name":"Senor Lopez Taqueria Mexican","address":"7146 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"789","name":"Red Park Inn Bar","address":"4442 Central ","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"715","name":"Yacht Club Exclusive","address":"7059 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"1283","name":"Papa's Pizza & Subs","address":"7801 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"1013","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #302","address":"7060 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"41684","inspectionDate":"2018-01-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)     FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES that are scaled only in Celsius or dually scaled in Celsius and Fahrenheit shall be accurate to ±1C in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n(B)     FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES that are scaled only in Fahrenheit shall be accurate to ±2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accurate","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Calibrate to requirement above."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"HOOD","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37369","inspectionDate":"2016-12-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"36788","inspectionDate":"2016-10-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand washing signage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In prep area","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5348"}}